Hello, I'm Marcy Collier-Overstreet, president of the Atlanta City Council.
On behalf of the entire city of Atlanta, I'm honored to be part of Celebration 120.
2026 represents a historical milestone in golf's Black history.
Clearview Golf Course, also known as America's Course,
would celebrate its 80th year of continuous operation by the family of William Powell,
a U.S. Army veteran who could not play golf at public golf courses upon his return
from serving our country, so he built his own.
Similarly, the National Black Golf Hall of Fame, founded by Harold Donovan,
and now run by his son Jeff, celebrates its 40th anniversary.
These two organizations have come together collectively to celebrate this historical moment.
120 years celebrating golf's Black history.
City of Atlanta is in the midst of a total renovation of its historic John A. White Golf Course,
where Jeff Donovan serves as its general manager.
John A. White will be the permanent home of the National Black Golf Hall of Fame
and will host the hall's 2027 induction weekend.
Obviously, the city is excited and honored to welcome the National Black Golf Hall of Fame
to Atlanta's storied and illustrious history.
We encourage each of you to support the celebration
120 event on Friday and Saturday, October 2nd and 3rd,
at Historic Clearview Golf Course in East Canton, Ohio.
To celebrate this historic golf moment, and it goes without saying,
when in Atlanta, come to the new John A. White and play around.
So join us in celebrating golf's Black history.
And remember, keep it in the short grass.